Doctor Durand. It's not safe.
We don't know if it's over.
She is out there. I have to find her.
I know where she was during the attack.
I can walk.
- I can't leave her.
- Listen to me.
If your sister's dead. I'm sorry.
There's nothing we can do for her.
If she's alive. where do you think she'd go?
She was on her way here...
You need to be here when she arrives.
Come on.
I'm talking to you!
Fred. throw him a bottle.
We don't know if there are other survivors.
The pulse destroyed all
the electrical circuits above ground.
The equipment we had with us
in the tunnel is okay.
We're rigging the generator.
Well?
Is there any radio chatter?
Nothing at all.
All the frequencies are dead.
Even the emergency band.
Keep searching.
Where are you going?
I need to check the array.
The dishes.
The colonel told me I could go.
Okay. go ahead.
Are you okay?
I keep thinking about my family.
Listen.
Which band is it on?
Not one of ours.
We don't use this frequency.
Where's it coming from?
Somewhere northeast of our position.
I can't be exact.
I've never heard this kind of signal.
Do you think it's extra-terrestrial?
I don't know.
Maybe they are already here?
Where is Doctor Durand?
What's your name?
Don't be afraid. you can tell me.
I'm Catherine. and you?
Where are your parents?
My dad said we had to run.
And then I hid in a cave.
Now I can't find them.
Where do you live?
In Grenoble.
I'm also going to Grenoble.
Come with me.
We will look for your parents together.
Who is Sophia?
...I heard you.
You were saying. "Sophia. Sophia!"
My sister.
Did you lose her too?
Yes.
Maybe she's with my mum and dad and brother.
Don't worry - they'll look after her as well.
I saw some people who were dead.
Try not to think about that.
Think of something else.
No noise. understand?
What are you doing?
Who's she?
I found her in the forest.
She lost her parents. Let her go.
Don't be scared.
They're friends. they want hurt you.
Why did you leave?
I had to find my sister.
I found her car up there.
But not her.
Perhaps she went back to Grenoble.
I can't let you go.
We don't know what's happening.
There could be another attack.
You don't have to come.
What are you going to do. shoot us?
We'll go but only because we need
to find out what's happening.
From now on. do exactly as I say.
Move when I say. stop when I say.
Is that clear?
Let's go.
Stay alert.
Civilians.
Where?
Close by the supermarket.
She could be with them.
Please.
Okay. let's go.
Where did they all go?
Set up a perimeter.
What is it?
Light!
Damn.
What the fuck?
On the roof!
Something on the roof!
Hold your fire!
Only on sight!
What's up there?
I don't know.
What is it?
No noise.
Cover me!
Put pressure on the wound.
Look after him.
Where are the doctor and the little girl?
What the fuck was that?
Did you see it?
- No.
- You OK?
Are you hurt?
Where's the kid?
Shit. What was that?
I don't know.
They're gone.
Don't look.
I'm sorry.
We've got to go. We can't stay here.
Too dangerous.
We can't leave her.
I've got men on the ground.
I've got no choice.
I'm sorry...
We should never have gone into the town.
I gave the order.
I should've protected her.
I should've done something.
There was nothing you could have done.
Did you see...
...what it was?
No.
But whatever it was. it was waiting for us.
I can't understand.
Why?
Maybe they see us as a threat?
They're scared of a little girl?
Then maybe we have something they want?
There are closer planets with resources.
Water and minerals.
Anything they might need.
It makes no sense.
It makes sense to them.
I'm going to bed.